<cast>
<item>
<name>Mai Lin</name>
<thumbnail>001mythmai.jpg</thumbnail>
<weapons>Sword</weapons>
<specialpower>None</specialpower>
<placeoforigin>New East</placeoforigin>
<discription>As one of the lucky few to escape the Mal's purging of the last Order of the Last Gods, she grew up in relative peace. However, her life would change the day she met Kenji, a goods trader. As the two grew closer, he confided that he was a part of the rebellion against the Mal. Kenji's execution at the hands of the Mal would serve as the catalyst that ended Mai Lin's life as a simple farm girl. With the death of her love, Mai Lin made the decision to join the rebellion. A master swordsman, Mai Lin was taught the art by her uncle who has a mysterious past all his own.</discription>
</item>
<item>
<name>Bushido</name>
<thumbnail>001mythbdo.jpg</thumbnail>
<weapons>None</weapons>
<specialpower>Above normal strength, agility <![CDATA[&]]> reflexes</specialpower>
<placeoforigin>New East</placeoforigin>
<discription>His name in the New East will inspire awe and fear from opponents <![CDATA[&]]> friends alike.
Bushido was the only one of the children of the Order that grew up under the protection of Daal and the high priests. Motivated to avenge the death of his father at the hands of Lord Tsu Lang, Bushido trained for years become perhaps the most powerful warrior in the world.

Due to his desire for revenge and hot temper, Bushido did not become the next leader of The Order.</discription>
</item>
<item>
<name>Adelaide</name>
<thumbnail>001mythadi.jpg</thumbnail>
<weapons>Sorcerer's staff</weapons>
<specialpower>Telekenetic/Energy Based</specialpower>
<placeoforigin>Old East</placeoforigin>
<discription>Before joining the Order of the Last Gods, rumor had it that Adelaide was one of the most dangerous pirates on the seas of the Old East. The origin of her mystical powers are also some what of a mystery, a reason why she is sometime reffered to as a witch by the Mal soldiers. Though fiercely loyal to the rest of the order, she is a very emotionally guarded.</discription>
</item>
<item>
<name>Anya</name>
<thumbnail>001mythmar.jpg</thumbnail>
<weapons>Western Broad Sword</weapons>
<specialpower>Low level energy based powers</specialpower>
<placeoforigin>New East</placeoforigin>
<discription>Though she is not fully trained, the light hearted and naive member of The Order surprises opponents with her skill level. Marylin works hard to earn the respect of the rest of The Order though she thinks the others are too serious. Often she plays pranks on Bushido to try to get him to expose his "nice" side.†

She joined The Order in the far reaches of the West Lands when she found a mysterious amulet in her home. Seeking the truth about her family, she travelled to the New East. She is often accompanied by Xui, a creature she found on her way to the New East.</discription>
</item>
</cast>